stretchingabuckblog.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Stretching a Buck | Stretching a Buck

Your privacy is very important to me. Accordingly, I have developed this policy in order for you to understand how I collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines my privacy policy.

## Stretching a Buck Media, LLC Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from [https://www.stretchingabuckblog.com](https://www.stretchingabuckblog.com/) (the “Site”).

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). This site and/or 3rd party advertisers on this site use(s) cookies. If you prefer, you can disable cookies via your browser, or opt out [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING**

I allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit my Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work)

You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting:

  * **FACEBOOK** – <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>
  * **GOOGLE** – <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>
  * **BING** – <https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

**DO NOT TRACK**  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**YOUR RIGHTS**  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**DATA RETENTION**  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**SUMMARY**

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, I will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * I will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by me and for other compatible purposes, unless I obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * I will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * I will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * I will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * I will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

**CHANGES**  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**CONTACT US**

I am committed to conducting my business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at stretchingabuck@gmail.com

_Updated 5/25/18_
